{"grammer" : {
    "quiz1" : {
      "question1" : {
        "question" : "Select the antonym of the word \"easy \".",
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1": "dark",
            "option2": "dead",
            "option3": "deep",
            "option4": "difficult"
        }
 
      },
      "question2" : {
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "XML",
            "option2" : "YML",
            "option3" : "HTML",
            "option4" : "JSX"
          },
        "question" : "____ tag syntax is used in React"
      },
      "question3" : {
        "correctoption" : "option1",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "Single root DOM node",
            "option2" : "Double root DOM node",
            "option3" : "Multiple root DOM node",
            "option4" : "None of the above"
          },
        "question" : "Application built with just React usually have ____"
      }
      
    },
    "quiz2" : {
      "question1" : {
        "question" : "Select the antonym of the word \"easy \".",
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1": "dark",
            "option2": "dead",
            "option3": "deep",
            "option4": "difficult"
        }
 
      },
      "question2" : {
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "XML",
            "option2" : "YML",
            "option3" : "HTML",
            "option4" : "JSX"
          },
        "question" : "____ tag syntax is used in React"
      },
      "question3" : {
        "correctoption" : "option1",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "Single root DOM node",
            "option2" : "Double root DOM node",
            "option3" : "Multiple root DOM node",
            "option4" : "None of the above"
          },
        "question" : "Application built with just React usually have ____"
      }
      
    }
  },
  "vocabulary":
  {
    "quiz1" : {
      "question1" : {
        "question" : "Select the antonym of the word \"easy \".",
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1": "dark",
            "option2": "dead",
            "option3": "deep",
            "option4": "difficult"
        }
 
      },
      "question2" : {
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "XML",
            "option2" : "YML",
            "option3" : "HTML",
            "option4" : "JSX"
          },
        "question" : "____ tag syntax is used in React"
      },
      "question3" : {
        "correctoption" : "option1",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "Single root DOM node",
            "option2" : "Double root DOM node",
            "option3" : "Multiple root DOM node",
            "option4" : "None of the above"
          },
        "question" : "Application built with just React usually have ____"
      }
      
    },
    "quiz2" : {
      "question1" : {
        "question" : "Select the antonym of the word \"easy \".",
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1": "dark",
            "option2": "dead",
            "option3": "deep",
            "option4": "difficult"
        }
 
      },
      "question2" : {
        "correctoption" : "option4",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "XML",
            "option2" : "YML",
            "option3" : "HTML",
            "option4" : "JSX"
          },
        "question" : "____ tag syntax is used in React"
      },
      "question3" : {
        "correctoption" : "option1",
        "options" : {
            "option1" : "Single root DOM node",
            "option2" : "Double root DOM node",
            "option3" : "Multiple root DOM node",
            "option4" : "None of the above"
          },
        "question" : "Application built with just React usually have ____"
      }
      
    }
  }
  }